呃喔  查莉被罚坐了  她犯什么事了
Uh-oh. Charlie's in a time-out. What'd she do?
她刚刚要把她弟弟交给邮递员
She tried to give your baby brother to the mailman.
嗯  连邮票都贴在他脑门上了
Mm-hmm. Even put a stamp on his forehead.
不是吧  PJ那时候不是也试过把我邮走吗
Wait a minute, didn't PJ try to mail me?
是啊  然后你试过邮走盖比  然后盖比试过邮走查莉
Yes, and you tried to mail Gabe, and Gabe tried to mail Charlie.
你看哈  这些甜蜜的家庭记忆电子邮件是带不来的
See, these are the sweet family memories you just don't get with e-mail.
是啊
Mm.
好吧
Okay.
查莉  知道自己哪里错了吗
Charlie, have you learned your lesson?
没有
No.
也就这样  出去玩吧  快点
Close enough. Get outta here. Go go go.
嗯  对了
Uh... Oh. Um...
顺便说一下  我今早看了一下你们学校的网站
By the way, I was on your school website this morning,
我刚好发现你们排球队需要一个团队管家
and I noticed that your volleyball team needs a team mom.
您应该没有考虑要致电去应聘吧
Don't tell me you're thinking about calling.
打过电话了
Called.
但  但是您应该不会就任的吧
But you're... You're not doing it, right?
就是我了
Doing it.
老妈  你不觉得我们应该先好好商量一下这件事情吗
Mom! Don't you think we should have had a conversation about this?
刚刚谈过了啊
Just did.
你笑什么笑
What are you smiling about?
下一个受苦的就是你了
It'll be your turn next.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite </i>
■
翻译： 不远景  Tracy
跳上车子 放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
■
校订： Enpistu
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby </i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
■
后期： Enpistu  liloelva
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby </i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Sure life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love</i> <i>who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第三季第十四集
Good Luck Charlie  S03E14  Team Mom
嘿  泰迪
Hey, Teddy.
你怎么穿这白大褂
What's with the lab coat?
哦  我在商场找到了一份新工作
Oh, I got a new job at the mall.
我现在是宾贝儿的香水调剂师
I'm a fragrance technician at Bimbel's.
- 香水调剂师  - 是啊
- Fragrance technician. - Mm-hmm.
我基本上就是拿一瓶香水然后  就这么喷
Basically, I hold up a bottle of cologne and do this... CHH.
反正和我在叽里咕噜炸鸡店
Very different from when I used to work
所做的工作大不同了  当时我做这种事
at Kwikki-Chikki, where I did this...
还有这个
And this...
有时候这样
And sometimes this...
哦  你现在试试这个
Oh. Now you try this.
把嘴拉上
Zip.
这就是棒球
This is baseball.
虽然不是我的最爱  但如果我看一场棒球
Not my favorite sport, but when I get to watch it,
就有了属于我自己的整整三个小时
I get three hours all to myself
- 嘿  老爸  - 怎么了
- Hey, dad. - Yeah?
我跟你说点事
There's something we need to talk about.
哦  别啊
Oh, no.
我需要找律师吗
Do I have to call my lawyer?
还是我的保险经理人  千万别说要两个都找
My insurance guy? Please don't say both.
别担心  你谁也不用找
Don't worry. You don't have to call anybody.
再说了  找麻烦的是十岁以前的盖比
Besides, trouble making was more tween Gabe's thing.
我已经过十岁了
I'm teen Gabe now.
那好  欢迎啊  我们
Well welcome Sir, we've uh...
都心神不宁的等这一天呢
Been nervously expecting you.
无所谓了  那好  事情是这样
All right. So, here's the thing.
明天  我需要你的帮忙  因为
Tomorrow, I need your help because...
我要和人约会了
I have a date.
不错啊  和哪位
Nice. So, who's the girl?
她叫艾玛  刚刚转到我们学校
Her name's Emma. She's new at our school.
好吧  就是说她不知道你的底细所以同意和你约会
Okay, so because she doesn't know you, she agreed to go out with you.
- 完全正确  - 早猜到了
- Exactly. - Yeah.
那好  计划是这样
Okay. So, here's the plan.
你来接我们  带我们去电影院
You pick us up, you take us to the theater,
然后尽量离我们有多远就坐多远
and you sit as far away from us as possible.
有问题么
Questions?
我能和她说话吗
Can I speak to her?
嗯  对了  我已经帮你准备好了闲聊剧本
Uh, yes. I have taken the liberty of preparing some small talk for you.
您好
"Hello."
我是鲍伯
"I'm Bob."
再见
"Good-bye."
其实  刚刚听你念出来
You know, now that I'm hearing it out loud...
我是鲍伯  这句也可以删掉
We may not need "I'm Bob."
嘿  埃米特  在死亡谷玩的怎么样
Hey, Emmett. How's the road trip to Death Valley?
车没油了
You ran out of gas?
那可不吉利啊
That can't be good.
还有秃鹰
Vultures?
那更不吉利了啊
That can't be good.
埃米特
Emmett.
拜托  兄弟  你绝对想不到
Dude, Emmett. You're not gonna believe this.
对门的小丑貌似搬走了
I think the clown moved out
现在那间公寓里住着一个漂亮美眉
because there's a really cute girl in that apartment.
你可无权先占先得
Well, you can't call dibs!
你没准都回不来了呢
We're not even sure if you're coming back.
抱歉了  老兄  我要出手了
Sorry, dude. I'm making my move.
哈
Yeah.
上去  下来
Up, and down.
上去
Up...
再下来
And down.
我听说这部电影很好看
I hear this movie is pretty good.
我也一样
Yeah, me too.
我也一样  就不能说点别的
Yeah, me too? That's all you got?
我应该给自己准备点台词卡的
I should have written out some cards for myself.
哦  太好了  谢了
Oh. Great, thanks.
我女儿在约会中
My daughter's on a date with a kid...
我得看着他们
And I'm keeping an eye on them.
巧了
You know what?
貌似和你女儿约会的是我的孩子
I think that's my kid she's on the date with.
- 鲍伯·邓肯  - 兰迪·斯克里比  近来如何
- Bob Duncan. - Randy Schleebee, how you doing?
还不错
I'm good.
吃点爆米花不
Have some popcorn.
好啊  谢了
Hmm? Thanks.
爆米花都给你了
Have all the popcorn.
哇  好咸
Whoa. Salty.
啐  沙士好难喝
Yuck. Root beer.
我的错
My bad.
哦  电影开始了
Oh, it's starting.
天啊  我们怎么又输了
Man, I can't believe we lost again.
你们认为问题出在哪
What do you think the problem is?
对手比我们的得分多
The other team scored more points than us.
- 嗯  我有个想法  - 别
- Um, I have an idea. - Mm!
别说  老妈  我们不是订过约法三章吗
Nope. Mom, remember we made an agreement.
作为团队管家  你只能回答有关食物和日程的问题
As team mom, you can only answer questions about snacks and schedules.
白纸黑字写着的
We even put this in writing.
如果她的建议和她切橙子的技术一样好
Well, if she gives advice as awesomely as she slices oranges,
她可能有一些好点子
maybe she's got something.
我喜欢她
I like this girl.
好了  姑娘们  大家听好了  我要给你们讲个故事
Okay, ladies. Listen up. I've got a story for you.
哦  千万别是您那些大学里的故事
Oh, just so long as it's not one of your college stories.
- 我上大学的时候  - 到底啊
- When I was in college... - Here we go.
我在西南丹佛社区大学冰雪聪明女子曲棍球队打球
I played hockey for the Southwest Denver Community College Lady Icers.
我们刚刚经历了十连败
We'd lost 10 games in a row.
但是这一窘境即将改变
But all that was about to change the night
那晚我们迎战我们的劲敌
that we played our arch rival,
东北普韦布洛社区大学淑女杀手队
the Northeast Pueblo Community College Lady Checkers.
你已经没地方买后悔药去了
This is time you're never gonna get back.
当时  天降暴雪  我们都住在一个汽车旅馆里
Now, because of a terrible blizzard, we had to stay in a motel.
那是我们经历的最好的事情
Best thing that ever happened to us.
我们彼此深入了解  并结下了深刻的友谊
We all got to know each other and we really bonded.
你们猜那场比赛上发生了什么
And you know what happened at the next game?
快说啊  我已经迫不急待了
No, but I'm on the edge of my seat.
她们队有个人从后面给我下绊
One of their players tripped me from behind...
然后我们全队冲向那个女孩
And our entire team jumped that girl
用横档犯规绊得她灵魂出窍
and cross-checked the daylights out of her.
炫啊
Ba-bam!
太感人了
It was so touching.
总结一下  你建议我们去袭击对手
To recap, your advice is that we attack someone?
别先动手
Well, not at first.
不  不  我是说你们应该邀请全队来举行一次睡衣晚会
No no no. I'm saying that you invite the team over for a slumber party.
- 这样你们就可以团结一心  - 我喜欢派对
- So you guys can all bond. - I love parties.
并且我最近买了一个新的睡袋
And I just got a new sleeping bag!
你有点太得瑟了
Okay, you are way too perky.
看样子我们要举行一次睡衣晚会了
Looks like we're having a sleepover.
我可以睡在我全新的睡袋里
Yes, in my new sleeping bag!
说真的  低调点
Seriously, just dial it down.
- 多好的一天啊  - 今天太悲惨了
- What a day. - What a day.
- 她离我好近  - 他离我太近了
- She sat so close. - He sat so close.
- 我们牵了手  - 他居然碰到了我的手
- Our hands touched. - Our hands touched!
等会  你在说谁
Wait, what are you talking about?
艾玛她爹
Emma's dad.
噩梦啊  我这辈子都不想再见到他了
What a total nightmare. I never want to see him again.
老爸  谁说你需要见到他了
Dad, who says you have to?
我和艾玛交往并不意味着你就要
Just because I'm hanging out with Emma doesn't mean that,
和她爸交往啊
you have to do stuff with her dad.
是么  我觉得兰迪可不这么想
Really? I don't think Randy feels the same way.
为什么
What do you mean?
因为他把电话号码写到了我的手上
Because he wrote his phone number on my hand.
固定电话
Home.
和手机号
And cell.
嘿
Hey.
- 我是茉莉  - 我叫PJ
- I'm Molly. - I'm PJ.
恭喜乔迁
Welcome to the neighborhood.
我真不知道我对面住着一个医生
I didn't know I was living across from a doctor.
啊  有吗
Oh, you are?
我是在说你啦  我看到你穿着白大褂
I was talking about you. I saw your coat.
哦  你以为
Oh. Oh, you think...
太难以置信了  如此年轻就可以成为一名医生
It's so impressive that someone so young could be a doctor.
我很用功
I've worked really hard.
你的专业是什么
So what's your specialty?
我的专业  呃
My specialty? I uh...
使人更好闻
Make people smell better.
哦  所以你是耳鼻喉科的
Oh, so you're an ear, nose, and throat guy?
主要是鼻子
Mostly nose.
大概百分之五十鼻子  百分之三十耳朵  百分之三十喉咙
I'd say it's 50% nose, 30% ear, 30% throat.
这都百分之一百一十了
That's 110%.
这是指我付出的努力
That's just how much I give.
你是做什么的茉莉
So what do you do, Molly?
哦  嗯  我在上大学
Oh, uh, I'm a college student.
好吧  很高兴见到你  PJ
Well, it was nice meeting you, PJ.
其实  嗯
You know, actually... Um.
我  啊
I, uh...
我在准备晚餐  如果你想来的话
I'm cooking dinner tonight if you want to come over.
主菜是烘肉卷
The diagnosis is meatloaf.
女士们  交流得怎么样了
Hey, girls. How's the bonding going?
好吧
Okay.
我知道问题出在哪了
I see what the problem is.
把你们的手机放到篮子里
Put your phones in the basket.
好  扔进去  进去
Good. Dump it. In.
哦  拜托
Aw, man.
泰迪
Teddy.
翁妮  你也是
Vonnie, you too.
- 要是我男朋友打电话来怎么办  - 你现在有男朋友了
- What if my boyfriend calls? - You have a boyfriend now?
给你
Here.
孩子们  忘掉你们的手机吧
Okay, girls. Forget about your phones.
好了  各位  我们来做一个沟通练习
Okay, everybody. We're gonna do a bonding exercise.
来  都起来  去那边站成一个圈
Now get up, get over there, form a circle.
快点快点  动起来
Let's go. Hustle, hustle. Get a move on.
好  把双手放在圈里并互相抓紧
Okay. Reach in the circle and grab two hands.
我们的目标是不放手并且解开这个结
Now the goal here is to untie the knot without letting go.
这很困难  但如果你们齐心合力就会发现其实很简单
It's very difficult, but if you work together, you'll see how easy it is.
开始
Go.
- 嗷  嗷  - 向这边转
- Ow. Ow. - Turn this way.
- 不行  另外一边  - 哎哟
- No, the other way! - Ow.
嗷  看着点
Ow, watch it!
你屁股顶着我的脸呢
Get your butt out of my face!
把你的脸拿开
Get your face out of my butt.
你们得好好学着怎么合作
You girls have got to learn to work together.
好的  我需要一个人自愿上来  泰迪  大家围着泰迪绕一个圈
Okay, I need a volunteer. Teddy. Everyone form a circle around Teddy.
快点
Come on.
现在  把你的眼睛闭上  把身体绷直
Now, you're going to close your eyes and make your body stiff and straight.
然后向圈外倒下
And then you're going to lean into the circle.
你以为自己会摔倒  其实并不会
Now, you're gonna feel like you're falling, but you're not
因为你的队友们会扶住你
because your teammates are going to keep you upright.
就是这样
There we go.
这就叫团队合作
Now we're working together.
很好  感觉如何啊  泰迪
Good. How you doing, Teddy?
- 很不错呢  - 很好
- You know, actually pretty good.  - Good.
啊
Aah!
我得随身带手机  因为我是当妈的
I have to have a phone, I'm a mom.
嗨  盖比
Hi, Gabe.
艾玛
Emma.
想一起出去吃冰淇淋吗
I was just wondering if you wanted to go out for ice cream.
- 当然  - 何不来个双人组呢
- Sure.  - Why not make it a foursome?
嘿  你都知道我家住哪了
Hey. Hey, you know where I live now.
那是当然了  小鲍
Come on, Bobbo.
咱今儿下午多开心哪  不把派对继续进行下去天理难容啊
We had so much fun this afternoon it'd be a crime not to keep the party going.
耶  喔
Yeah... Oh, whoa.
我说盖比  帮个忙啊
Come on, Gabe. A little help?
你闻上去像花儿一样香
You smell like flowers.
那啥  是这样的
Oh, you... You know what? What am I thinking?
我哪也去不了  我还有俩小的要照顾
I can't go anywhere, I got two little ones I gotta take care of.
我听到了  鲍哥
I hear you, Bobsled.
这是赤裸裸的呼救啊
That's a cry for help.
我怎么能撇下你不管
So I'm staying right here with you.
那我们就在这吃冰淇淋吧
Maybe we can just have ice cream here.
看来要在家里开趴了  鲍小喵
Looks like the party's staying home, Bobcat.
你也听到了  我给你起了好几个昵称
As you can tell, I've been thinking of some nicknames for you.
你也给我想几个呗
So you think of some names for me.
正想着呢
Oh, I am.
现在我们要做另一个沟通练习
Okay, we are going to do another bonding exercise.
每个人找个搭档
Everyone find a partner.
好了
Okay, good.
现在我要每个人告诉对方一个你喜欢她的地方
Now I want each of you to tell your partner one thing you like about her...
以及不喜欢的
And one thing you don't.
完了大家就会更亲密了
By the end of this, we're all gonna be very close.
啥  你说我脑袋太大
Oh yeah? Yeah, my head's too big?
是你脑袋太小
Well, your head is too small!
我才没有过分戏剧化
I am not over dramatic!
还说没有
She said over dramatically.
等等
Oh, wait a sec.
是我的错
My bad.
还真是好玩
This is actually really funny.
这个其实不是沟通练习啦
Um, this is not a bonding exercise.
我们上表演课时这么干以让情绪崩溃
No. We did this in my acting class to break down our emotions.
我感觉自己一无是处
I feel so worthless!
瞧瞧  效果显著啊
Well, as you can see, it's very effective.
翁妮  你比哈姆斯通教练还要恶毒
You know what, Vonnie? You're even meaner than Coach Hammerstone!
得了吧  才没人比那个双元音恶毒
Oh, please. Nobody's meaner than that diphthong.
- 就是  史上最差  - 我恨他
- Yeah, the worst. - I hate him.
- 你们不喜欢教练  - 是恨死了
- We don't like the coach?  - Hate him.
别人我都喜欢
And I like everybody.
那就行了
Well... Well, that's it.
把队员紧密连在一起的最好事物莫过于
The best thing any team can bond over...
一个公众之敌
A common enemy.
拿上外套
Grab your coats.
那睡衣派对呢
Wait. What about the slumber party?
甭担心
Oh, don't worry.
等咱羞辱完了教练再回来开
After we humiliate the coach, we'll all come back here and get in our jammies.
如果非得说从这么些年的行医生涯中学到了什么
If there's one thing I've learned from all my years of doctoring...
那必须是  棍棒和石头可以打断骨头
It's that sticks and stones can break your bones.
- 很高兴你告诉我  - 嗯
- Good to know.  - Mm-hmm.
茉莉  你知道之前你的公寓住的是谁吗
You know who used to live in your apartment, Molly?
一个小丑
A clown.
对啊  是派切斯  我从他那转租的
Oh, right. Patches. I'm subletting from him.
他在艘游轮上工作
He's working on a cruise ship.
船和小丑
Boats and clowns.
呃  我最害怕的两个东西
Ugh, two of my biggest fears.
其实我最最害怕的应该是
Actually my biggest fear...
一艘由小丑开的
Would be a boat full of spiders...
装满蜘蛛的船
Driven by a clown.
好吧
Okay.
咱能撤了吗
So, shall we retire to the...
到那边
Over there?
能请你帮个忙吗
Hey, can I ask you something?
当然
Sure.
我从自行车上摔下来把肘擦伤了
I fell off my bike and scraped my elbow.
可能感染了
I think it might be infected.
- 你能给看下吗  - 呃
- Would you take a look?  - Oh, um.
我是耳鼻喉科的
I'm ear, nose, and throat.
你该找臂腕肘科的医生看啊
You need more of a wrist, elbow, armpit guy.
怎么说你也是医生呀
Still. You are a doctor, right?
可不是呢嘛
Got me there.
让我看下
Okay. Let's take a look.
好恶  好恶  好恶  好恶
Ewe ewe ewe ewe ewe ewe ewe!
太恶心了
That's disgusting.
- 感染了吗  - 赶紧给遮上
- Is it infected?  - It's something. Cover it up!
哦
Oh! Ohh.
我现在宁愿在小丑开的蜘蛛船上
Oh, I would rather be on the spider clown boat right now.
PJ
PJ?
你不是医生  对吗
You're not really a doctor, are you?
嗯
No.
我不是
I'm not. I...
我只是在宾贝儿店里喷香水的
Spray cologne at Bimbel's Department store.
那你为什么要骗我
Why did you lie?
因为你好像很喜欢医生
Because you seemed so impressed by all the doctor stuff.
我觉得如果你知道我真正的身份就不会喜欢我了
I didn't think you'd like me if you knew what I really do.
对不起
I'm sorry.
嗯
Well...
其实吧
Actually...
我也没有完全对你说实话
I wasn't completely honest with you either.
啥意思
What do you mean?
我并不是学生
I'm not really a student.
那你是啥
What are you?
还真“惊喜”啊
This is a surprise.
我通常不会第一次约会就告诉对方
I don't usually tell people on the first date,
不过这样好像也挺自然的
but it kind of came up naturally.
好吧好吧
Okay okay okay.
我需要点时间消化一下
I just need some time to get used to this.
很多人都害怕小丑  不过我会帮你克服的  PJ
PJ, a lot of people are afraid of clowns, but I can help you get over that.
好的好的
Okay okay okay. Um...
咱明天开始呗
We'll start tomorrow.
接招吧  哈姆斯通
Take that, Hammerstone!
- 喔  - 帅
- Whoa.  - Yes.
让你尝尝我的双层纸卷弹
Yeah, taste my two-ply fury!
- 好身手  帅呆了翁妮  - 耶
- Great shot, Vonnie. You rock!  - Yeah!
继续开火  姑娘们
Keep firing, girls.
击倒烟囱的奖励五块钱
Five bucks if anyone can get it down the chimney.
快看哪  真的是在团队合作呢
Look at this. We're really coming together as a team.
你的主意还真起作用了
Your idea actually worked.
那是当然了  你有啥好惊讶的
Well, of course it worked. Why are you surprised?
我也说不好  可能是之前留下阴影了吧
I don't know, maybe I've been influenced by the last,
五十个主意都没起过作用
50 ideas that went so horribly wrong.
我说  以后你得相信你家老娘
Well, maybe in the future you'll give your old mom some credit.
我知道我在做什么
She knows what she's doing.
邓肯阿姨
Mrs. Duncan?
为啥哈姆斯通教练家门口的擦鞋垫上写的是“强森家”呢
Why does Coach Hammerstone's welcome mat say "The Johnsons"?
啥
Huh?
这不是白桦路北306室吗
Is is 306 North Birchwood, right?
这是白桦路南306室
This is 306 South Birchwood.
这可扯了
Bummer.
快跑
Run!
啊
Aah!
没被抓住的去白桦路北306室集合
Whoever doesn't get arrested, meet me at 306 North Birchwood!
等等  别开门
Wait wait wait. Don't answer that.
盖比  我是艾玛
Gabe, it's Emma.
你在家吗
Are you home?
这是个计谋
It's a trick.
我知道他在外面
I know he's out there.
说我不在
I'm not here.
艾玛
Emma.
还有兰德侠
And the Rand-man.
我没吱声是为了逗你老爸玩的
I didn't want to say anything so I could trick your dad.
鲍兄呢
So, where is the Ka-Bobster?
呃
Um...
他不在家
He's not home.
他在家
Yes, he is.
不  不在
Uh, no. No he's not.
每次老爸走她都会哭所以我们骗她来着
She falls apart every time he leaves so we try to keep her out of the loop.
他在后面
He's in there.
我爱死这家伙了  总逗我玩
Oh, I love this guy. Always playing games.
- 抓到你了  - 嘿
- Gotcha!  - Hey.
坐呗
So, want to sit down?
嗯
Sure.
我们的爸爸是好朋友  真是太好了
Isn't it great that our dads are best friends?
关于这事吧
Yeah, about that.
呃
Um...
事实上
The truth is...
我爸不怎么喜欢你爸
My dad isn't crazy about your dad.
啥  我爸怎么了
What? What's wrong with my dad?
首先  他太闹了
For one thing, he's kind of loud.
他那是开朗
He's outgoing.
还总起一堆傻缺的外号
He makes up a bunch of stupid nicknames.
鲍兄  多有趣的外号啊
Ka-Bobster? That's hilarious.
还有  他舔手指吃别人的食物
I mean, he licks his fingers and eats other people's food.
没错
Yeah.
这个我想不出理由了
I've got nothing for that one.
不过你老爸也不是多优秀
You know, your dad's not exactly perfect.
脾气坏  邋遢  冒傻气
He's grumpy, and messy, and says stupid things...
喔喔喔
Whoa whoa whoa.
问题可不在于我爸
My dad's not the problem.
在于你爸
Yours is.
我是说
I mean, yeah.
我爸是有问题  不过这次的问题不在他
My dad is a problem, but not this problem.
我不敢相信你竟然说我爸的坏话
Well, I can't believe you're saying bad things about my dad.
爸  我们走
Daddy? Let's go!
- 怎么了  亲爱的  - 我想走了
- What's wrong, honey?  - I want to go.
盖比就是个混球
Gabe's a jerk.
哦是吗
Oh... Oh yeah? Well...
你闻起来再也没有花香的味道了
You don't smell like flowers any more!
说得好
Good one.
可不是呢嘛
Wasn't it?
哇  还真是震惊啊
Wow. This is a shock.
看来咱俩也不能做朋友了
Hey, I guess this is it for us, too, huh?
咱孩子闹翻了不代表咱俩就不能在一起玩了啊
Just because the kids aren't seeing each other doesn't mean that we can't.
我有个好主意
Hey, I got a great idea.
我们去露营吧
Let's go camping.
我有个更好的注意
Hey, I got a better idea.
是啥呀
What is it?
好了  小查莉
Well, Charlie.
老妈又一次的介入我的活动
Um, once again mom interfered with one of my activities,
不过这次呢还真是帮上忙了
but this time she actually helped.
多亏她  我们队比以前更紧密了
Yeah, thanks to her, the team really bonded.
等做法院命令的社区服务的时候
And, uh, we'll have a chance to bond even more
估计会更紧密
at our court-ordered community service.
你好
Hello?
找谁
Who?
鲍伯喇嘛丁当
Bob-a-lama-ding-dong?
- 说我不在  - 哈哈  你在
- I'm not here.  - Oh, yes you are!
啧啧  看来鲍伯喇嘛丁当交个新朋友嘛
Well, it looks like Bob-a-lama-ding-dong has a new friend.
咳
Ooh.
祝他好运吧  小查莉
Wish him good luck, Charlie.
泰迪亲  那不是真的
Teddy, honey, it's not true.
她们嘴太坏了
Those girls were just being mean.
真的吗
Are you sure?
当然了
Yes, I'm sure.
你脑袋不大
You do not have a big head.
你确定你不是在安慰我
You're not just saying that?
当然不是了
No. No.
很多家庭都需要把门加宽的
Lots of families have to have their doors widened.
不过最近我感觉
It's just that lately I've been feeling Like it's...
脑袋比以前大了
Bigger than usual.
那估计是因为跟你兄弟们呆在一起的时间太长了
Well, that's because You've been spending too much time with your brothers.
说啥呢你们
Hey, guys. What's going on?
你看啥呢
What you looking at?